let mission_core_values_questions_repo = {
    "1": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "It is the mission of the Los Angeles Police Department to safegaurd the lives and property of the people we serve, to reduce the incidence and fear of crime, and to enhance public safety while working with the diverse communities to improve their quality of life. What is our mandate?",
        "answer1": "To execute our mission with integrity and professionalism, at all times serving those in need",
        "answer2": "To execute our mission with honor and integrity, while at all times conducting ourselves with the highest ethical standards to maintain public confidence",
        "answer3": "To serve the public good with integrity and honor, while upholding the highest standards of public safety",
        "answer4": "To ensure public safety, peace, and welfare",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
    },
    "2": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the vision of the Los Angeles Police Department?",
        "answer1": "To uphold the highest levels of integrity, to keep the public peace, and to create a safe city for all",
        "answer2": "To, as closely as possible, achieve a city that is safe, secure, and peaceful for all",
        "answer3": "To, as closely as possible, achieve a City free from crime and public disorder",
        "answer4": "To serve with integrity, keep the public peace, and uphold justice",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
    },
    "3": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "The Los Angeles Police Department is committed to serving the community while protecting the rights of all persons. Consistent with this commitment, the Department’s Vision, Mission and Core Values, in concert with the Law Enforcement Code of Ethics and the Department’s Management Principles, reflect the guiding philosophy of the Los Angeles Police Department. What is this statement known as?",
        "answer1": "The Preamble",
        "answer2": "The Vision",
        "answer3": "The Mission",
        "answer4": "The Mandate",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
    },
    "4": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "It is the ______ of the Los Angeles Police Department to, as closely as possible, achieve a City free from crime and public disorder. What is this statement known as?",
        "answer1": "The Preamble",
        "answer2": "The Vision",
        "answer3": "The Mission",
        "answer4": "The Mandate",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
    },
    "5": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "It is the _______ of the Los Angeles Police Department to safeguard the lives and property of the people we serve, to reduce the incidence and fear of crime, and to enhance public safety while working with the diverse communities to improve their quality of life. Our mandate is to do so with honor and integrity, while at all times conducting ourselves with the highest ethical standards to maintain public confidence. What is this statement known as?",
        "answer1": "The Preamble",
        "answer2": "The Vision",
        "answer3": "The Mission",
        "answer4": "The Mandate",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
    },
    "6": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is our motto and also our way of life?",
        "answer1": "To serve with honor and integrity",
        "answer2": "To keep the public peace and safety",
        "answer3": "To serve our customers",
        "answer4": "To protect and serve",
        "correctAnswer": "answer4"
    },
    "7": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the first line of the service to our communities core value?",
        "answer1": "We are dedicated to enhancing public safety and reducing the fear and the incidence of crime.",
        "answer2": "Working with the Los Angeles Police Department should be challenging and rewarding.",
        "answer3": "We will strive to achieve the highest level of quality in all aspects of our work.",
        "answer4": "We have been given the honor and privilege of enforcing the law.",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
    },
    "8": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the first line of the reverence for the law core value?",
        "answer1": "Working with the Los Angeles Police Department should be challenging and rewarding.",
        "answer2": "We have been given the honor and privilege of enforcing the law.",
        "answer3": "Integrity is our standard.",
        "answer4": "We will strive to achieve the highest level of quality in all aspects of our work.",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
    },
    "9": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the first line of the commitment to leadership core value?",
        "answer1": " We are dedicated to enhancing public safety and reducing the fear and the incidence of crime.",
        "answer2": "We will strive to achieve the highest level of quality in all aspects of our work.",
        "answer3": "We believe the Los Angeles Police Department should be a leader in Law Enforcement.",
        "answer4": "We must each work to ensure that our co-workers, our professional colleagues and our communities have the highest respect for the Los Angeles Police Department.",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
    },
    "10": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the first line of the integrity in all we say and do core value?",
        "answer1": "We will demonstrate honest, ethical behavior in all our interactions.",
        "answer2": "Our actions will match our words.",
        "answer3": "We must aim for continuous improvement in serving the people in our communities.",
        "answer4": "Integrity is our standard.",
        "correctAnswer": "answer4"
    },
    "11": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the first line of the respect for people core value?",
        "answer1": "We believe in treating all people with respect and dignity.",
        "answer2": "We will strive to achieve the highest level of quality in all aspects of our work.",
        "answer3": "We believe the Los Angeles Police Department should be a leader in Law Enforcement.",
        "answer4": "Working with the Los Angeles Police Department should be challenging and rewarding.",
        "correctAnswer": "answer4"
    },
    "12": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the first line of the quality through continuous improvement core value?",
        "answer1": "We will strive to achieve the highest level of quality in all aspects of our work.",
        "answer2": "Our people are our most important resource.",
        "answer3": "Our personal and professional behavior should be a model for all to follow.",
        "answer4": "People in our communities are our most important customers.",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
    },
    "13": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What are our core values?",
        "answer1": "Reverence for the law, Service to our communities, Integrity and Honor, Service to our leaders, Quality through continuous improvement",
        "answer2": "Respect for people, Reverence for the law, Commitment to our communities, Integrity in all we say and do, Upholding high ethical standards",
        "answer3": "Service to our communities, Reverence for the law, Commitment to leadership, Integrity in all we say and do, Respect for people, Quality through continuous improvement",
        "answer4": "Quality through continuous improvement, Service to our communities, Service to our customers, Integrity in all we say and do, Respect for people",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
    },
    "14": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Service to our communities core value, fill in the blank: We will work in ______ with the people in our communities and do our best, within the law, to solve community problems that affect public safety. We value the great _____ of people in both our residential and business communities and serve all with _____ dedication.",
        "answer1": "partnership, diversity, equal",
        "answer2": "cooperation, diversity, fair",
        "answer3": "union, spirit, equal",
        "answer4": "cooperation, diversity, equal",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
    },
    "15": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Reverence for the law core value, fill in the blank: We must always exercise ______ in the use of the ______ and authority that have been given to us by the ______.",
        "answer1": "caution, faculty, people",
        "answer2": "integrity, power, people",
        "answer3": "goodwill, power, city",
        "answer4": "integrity, law, chief",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
    },
    "16": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Commitment to leadership core value, fill in the blank: We must each work to ensure that our ______, our professional colleagues and our ______ have the highest ______ for the Los Angeles Police Department.",
        "answer1": "fellow-officers, leaders, respect",
        "answer2": "colleagues, customers, regard",
        "answer3": "co-workers, communities, respect",
        "answer4": "colleagues, communities, respect",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
    },
    "17": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Integrity in all we say and do core value, fill in the blank: We will demonstrate ______, ______ behavior in all our interactions. Our ______ will match our words.",
        "answer1": "bold, honest, actions",
        "answer2": "honest, diligent, behaviors",
        "answer3": "integral, trustworthy, behaviors",
        "answer4": "honest, ethical, actions",
        "correctAnswer": "answer4"
    },
    "18": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Respect for people core value, fill in the blank: We can best serve the many and varied needs of our communities by ______ our employees to fulfill their responsibilities with ______, authority and appropriate ______.",
        "answer1": "empowering, knowledge, discretion",
        "answer2": "developing, integrity, behavior",
        "answer3": "supporting, efficiency, professionalism",
        "answer4": "inspiring, honor, action",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
    },
    "19": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Quality through continuous improvement core value, fill in the blank: We must aim for continuous ______ in serving the people in our communities. We value ______ and support ______.",
        "answer1": "engagement, integrity, officers",
        "answer2": "improvement, innovation, creativity",
        "answer3": "development, people, growth",
        "answer4": "growth, innovation, creativity",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
    },
    "20": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Our personal and professional behavior should be a model for all to follow. We will obey and support the letter and the spirit of the Law. Which core value does this belong to?",
        "answer1": "Service to our communities",
        "answer2": "Commitment to leadership",
        "answer3": "Reverence for the law",
        "answer4": "Respect for people",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
    },
    "21": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "We also believe that each individual needs to be a leader in his or her area of responsibility. Which core value does this belong to?",
        "answer1": "Respect for people",
        "answer2": "Quality through continuous improvement",
        "answer3": "Service to our communities",
        "answer4": "Commitment to leadership",
        "correctAnswer": "answer4"
    },
    "22": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "We must have the courage to stand up for our beliefs and do what is right. Which core value does this belong to?",
        "answer1": "Integrity in all we say and do",
        "answer2": "Commitment to leadership",
        "answer3": "Reverence for the law",
        "answer4": "Quality through continuous improvement",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
    },
    "23": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Integrity in all we say and do core value, fill in the blank: Throughout the ranks, the Los Angeles Police Department has a long history of ______ and ______ from ______. Upholding this proud tradition is a challenge we must all continue to meet.",
        "answer1": "professionalism, commitment, officers",
        "answer2": "integrity, freedom, corruption",
        "answer3": "honor, integrity, officers",
        "answer4": "integrity, trust, citizens",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
    },
    "24": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "We encourage our people to submit ideas, we listen to their suggestions, and we help them develop to their maximum potential. Which core value does this belong to?",
        "answer1": "Quality through continuous improvement",
        "answer2": "Commitment to leadership",
        "answer3": "Respect for people",
        "answer4": "Service to our communities",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
    },
    "25": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Respect for people core value, fill in the blank: We believe in treating all people with respect and ______. We show concern and ______ for the victims of crime and treat ______ of the law with fairness and dignity.",
        "answer1": "courtesy, compassion, violators",
        "answer2": "dignity, compassion, criminals",
        "answer3": "decency, empathy, violators",
        "answer4": "dignity, empathy, violators",
        "correctAnswer": "answer4"
    },
    "26": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "We realize that constant change is a way of life in a dynamic city like Los Angeles, and we dedicate ourselves to proactively seeking new and better ways to serve. Which core value does this belong to?",
        "answer1": "Quality through continuous improvement",
        "answer2": "Respect for people",
        "answer3": "Service to our communities",
        "answer4": "Commitment to leadership",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
    }
}